Prerequisite：
You may need:
1、Visual Studio to run the project on server
2、SQL Server(change the database address in the 'appsettings.json', then enter 'add migration migration-name' and 'update-database' command to create database on the Package Manager Console)
3、install calibre as format conversion tool
4、run the server and client


On the main site, you may login with admin:
zhengqi_cai@outlook.com 
Test@123

or register other accounts, then add books on the homepage on view online

On the readoline page, you could navigate content with category, scale view and add comments which can be tracked to created pages.

You can also manage the content by client GUI.